blogcatalog.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy | BlogCatalog

**Introduction**

AdSeek Media LLC ( **“Company”** or **  “We”**) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit blogcatalog.com (our “ **Website** “) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, you may choose not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Children Under the Age of 14**

Our Website is not intended for children under 14 years of age. No one under age 14 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 14. If you are under 14, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 14 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including (i) personal information that you submit to us if and when you create a user profile, (ii) information that you post, submit, publish, display or transmit to other users on the Website (your “ **User Contributions** ”), and (iii) information that is automatically collected as you navigate through the Website, including cookies and other data collection and tracking technologies.  The information we collect automatically may include personal information, which helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service.

**Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We may also enable site developers with access to APIs to collect and display certain information from the Website.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy to comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request, or to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or Blog Content License Agreement.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an email at support@blogcatalog.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Use.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to support@blogcatalog.com.

**Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where you have chosen a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at support@blogcatalog.com.
